A Finding Aid to the Nancy Spero Papers, 1940s-2009, in the Archives of American Art AAA.spernanc
Archives of American Art
- Photographic Material, 1940s-2009; Series 8; 1 Linear feet Boxes 25-26, 29
  - Artwork by Spero (Box 25)
    - Notes in Time on Women, Part II, undated; 1979 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Torture of Women, Slides, 1976-1979 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - War Series, Slides, undated (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Artwork by Other Artists, 1987-2001; undated (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Exhibition Installations (Box 26)
    - Azure Installation, Galerie Lelong, New York (2002), circa 2002 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - "Dissidances," Amsterdam (2008) (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - "Dissidances," Sofia Reina (2008 October 14-2009 January 5), 2008-circa 2009 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - "Dissidances," Unidentified Venue, circa 2008-circa 2009 (Box 26, Folder 4-7)
    - Galerie Monteney, Paris, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Riverside Studios (1984 July 18-August 12) (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Sacred and Profane Installation, New York Kunsthalle (1966), circa 2000s (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Smith College Museum of Art, circa 1990 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Toronto Waterworks Project (1988 June) (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - "Venice Biennale, 52" (2007 June 10-November 21) (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Unidentified, undated (Box 26, Folder 14-15)
  - People (Box 26)
    - Artaud, undated; Oversized material housed in Box 29 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Nancy Spero, 1940s-2005; Oversized material housed in Box 29 (Box 26, Folder 17-19)
    - Nancy Spero and Leon Golub, circa 2000-2004 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - Nancy Spero and Leon Golub in Salzburg, Austria, circa 1995 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - Family, undated; 1960-2000s (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Friends, undated; 1990s-2000s (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Places, Unidentified, undated; 2000-circa 2007 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Miscellaneous Subjects, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Photograph Album, circa 2000s (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Oversized Photographs of People from Box 26, folders 16-19, 1940s-2005; undated (Box 29)
- Video Recordings, 1970s-1990s; Series 9; 1 Linear feet Boxes 26-28
  This series consists of 18 videocassettes (VHS). Many include no identifying information while others are too vaguely labeled to determine the series with which they belong.
  Additional audiovisual materials can be found among the biographical materials (Series 1), interviews (Series 3), writings (Series 4), and subject files (Series 5).
  - "L & N, I-VI", 1970s; 6 Videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 26, Folder 27-29)
  - "L& N, VII", undated; 1 Videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - "Nancy and Leon", 1980s; 4 videocassette (Hi8) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - "Spero Golub", 1990s; 1 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Unlabeled, 1970s; 1 Videocassettes (U-matic) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Unlabeled, 1990s; 5 Videocassettes (VHS) (Box 28, Folder 1-2)